exadel.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy | Exadel

### 1\. General Provisions and Objectives

This Privacy Policy describes Exadel’s policies and practices regarding the collection and use of your personal data, and sets forth your privacy rights. We recognize that information privacy is an ongoing responsibility, and so we will from time to time update this Policy as we undertake new personal data practices or adopt new privacy policies.

### 2\. Policy Scope

Using this Site, you agree with terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy and Conditions of Use and/or any other agreement that we might have with you.

You agree that any dispute over privacy or terms contained in this Privacy Policy or any other agreement the Company has with you, will be governed by the laws of Lithuania.

Exadel reserves the right to amend the Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason, without prior notice to you **.** You can see the latest Policy change date at the footer.

### 3\. What information does Exadel collect?

When you use our Site, we may collect Personal Information that you chose to provide to us. For example, in our “Contact Us”, you provide us contact information. When you submit a CV, this means that you give us your consent to process it and contact you when necessary.

We may also collect certain information related to your device, such as your device IP address and referring Site.

#### 3.1 Contact forms

Some pages on our website have contact forms. When you leave a message or submit a CV, you are asked for some basic information about you. This information is then stored in our Database and later may be used to contact you with something relevant to your initial request. Data from contact forms come to our Delivery Team, CVs are directed to the HR Team.

#### 3.2 Logs of web server

This website is located on our dedicated server which is supported by Exadel IT Department. It collects some technical information including IP addresses of the visitors. These data are used only for troubleshooting and never go outside of the support team.

### 4\. Cookies and analytics

We also use information to administer and improve our Website and to analyze use of the Website for marketing and advertising purposes and trend monitoring. Cookies are used for these purposes.

Cookie is a small file on your device with a string of letters and numbers which serve as a unique identifier. Sometimes cookies can also be used to store your personal preferences on websites or to save your login data. There are no personal data in cookies.

When you open this website, cookies are created on your device. When your open it next time, cookies are sent back to us letting us know you’ve already been there. 

#### 4.1 Types of cookies

The following type of cookies are used:

  * Analytics Cookies – These cookies collect aggregated information about how visitors use a Website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and whether they received error messages from web pages. These cookies do not collect information that identifies you. All the information these cookies collect is anonymous and is only used to provide statistical information about our Website as a whole.
  * Content Cookies – These cookies are used to perform tests on various aspects of our Website and ensure a consistent user experience. These cookies do not collect information that identifies you. All the information these cookies collect is anonymous and is only used to improve how our Website works.

#### 4.2 List of used cookies 

**Cookie** | **Purpose** | **Lifetime**  
---|---|---  
**Analytics Cookies**  
1P_JAR | Google Analytics | One (1) month  
DV | Google Analytics | Ten (10) minutes  
NID | Google Analytics | Six (6) months  
UULE | Google Analytics | One (1) day  
_ga | This cookie is used by Google Analytics and contains a visitor’s unique and random ID number. | Two (2) years  
_gid | Google Analytics | One (1) day  
nQ_cookield | Albacross tracking: [https://albacross.com/](https://albacross.com/) | 80 years  
nQ_visitld | Albacross tracking: [https://albacross.com/](https://albacross.com/) | 80 years  
**Content Cookies**  
_icl_visitor_lang_js  | WPML plugin for translation: [https://wpml.org/](https://wpml.org/) |   
wpml_browser_redirect_test | One (1) session  
calltrk_landing | CallRail tracking: [https://www.callrail.com/](https://www.callrail.com/) | One (1) year  
calltrk_refferrer | CallRail tracking: [https://www.callrail.com/](https://www.callrail.com/) | One (1) year  
calltrk_session_id | CallRail tracking: [https://www.callrail.com/](https://www.callrail.com/) | One (1) year  
referrerURL | Contains Referrer URL for Sales Force integration. | One (1) session  
  
**We cannot identify your personality** using the above statistics because we see only aggregated and anonymized data. If you don’t want your behavior to be tracked, simply disable cookies in your browser. Please note that this and other websites may not work as expected if cookies were switched off.

This website contains links to various third party websites (Facebook, Linkedin, Twitter etc.) Exadel has no control over, and is not responsible for the content, privacy policies or reliability of such sites.

### 5\. Disclosure to Third Parties

This website is located in the Netherlands, all data collection happens here.

Exadel has its offices in different countries (including countries with no adequate protection).  You can find the list of all offices [here](https://exadel.com/about/locations/). The data collected by Exadel may be transferred to our offices.

Exadel relies on derogations for specific situations as set forth in Article 49 of the GDPR. In particular, Exadel collects and transfers personal data to the different offices only: 

  * with your consent;
  * or to fulfill a compelling legitimate interest of Exadel in a manner that does not outweigh your rights and freedoms. 

Exadel endeavors to apply suitable safeguards to protect privacy and security of your personal data and to use it only consistent with your relationship with Exadel and the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

Exadel also minimizes the risk to your rights and freedoms by not collecting or storing sensitive information about you.

### 6\. Security of your information

To help protect the privacy of data and personally identifiable information you transmit through the use of this Site, we maintain physical, technical and administrative safeguards.

We update and test our security technology on an ongoing basis. We restrict access to your personal data to those employees who need to know that information.

In addition, we train our employees about the importance of confidentiality and maintaining the privacy and security of your information. We commit to taking appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce our employees’ privacy responsibilities.

### 7\. Data subject rights

You can always opt not to disclose information to us. You can set or amend your web browser controls to accept or reject cookies. If you do, you may still use our Website, but some access to functionality may be restricted.

### 8\. Data storage and retention

We don’t have retention period for your data which are collected from contact forms at this website. We keep it to be able to reach you out when we have something relevant to your initial request (for example, job offers if you submitted your CV).

Retention period for the logs of our web server is set to 14 days, also we have indexed copies of logs with the retention period of 35 and 365 days.

Retention period for the data which are collected at this website by third party providers (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn) is set by them and is a subject of their terms and privacy policies.
